She's having the time of someone else's life.
Monte Carlo is a adventure, comedy, romance film directed by Thomas Bezucha.
Three young women vacationing in Paris find themselves whisked away to Monte
Carlo after one of the girls is mistaken for a British heiress.
Grace / Cordelia Winthrop Scott, played by Selena Gomez.
Emma, played by Katie Cassidy.
Meg, played by Leighton Meester.
Owen, played by Cory Monteith.
Pam, played by Andie MacDowell.
Robert, played by Brett Cullen.
Monte Carlo is a 2011 American adventure-romantic comedy film based on the
2001 novel Headhunters by Rankin/Bass co-founder Jules Bass.
It was directed by Thomas Bezucha.
Denise Di Novi, Alison Greenspan, Nicole Kidman, and Arnon Milchan
produced the film for Fox 2000 Pictures and Regency Enterprises.
It began production in Harghita, Romania on May 5, 2010.
Monte Carlo stars Selena Gomez, Leighton Meester and Katie Cassidy as three
friends posing as wealthy socialites in Monte Carlo, Monaco.
The film was released on July 1, 2011.
It features the song "Who Says" by Selena Gomez & the Scene (whose album When the Sun Goes Down which included the
song, was released 3 days before the film's release) and numerous songs by British singer Mika.
Monte Carlo received mixed reviews from critics, but
earned $39.7 million on a $20 million budget.
Fox Home Entertainment released Monte Carlo on DVD
and Blu-ray Disc on October 18, 2011.
The film explores themes of monte carlo, mistaken
identity, look-alike, young woman, texan.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.